mobilicity.ca 2013-06-07

# 

                                  Privacy Policy
This agreement is strictly confidential and proprietary to Data & Audio-Visual Enterprises Wireless Inc.
“Mobilicity” and the logo are trademarks of Data & Audio-Visual Enterprises Wireless Inc. Distribution, copy
or any other use of this agreement and/or the trademarks without the written consent of Data & Audio-Visual
Enterprises Wireless Inc. is strictly prohibited.

 Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY
INFORMATION WE COLLECT
Data & Audio-Visual Enterprises Wireless Inc. and its affiliates ("Mobilicity"), have adopted a
privacy policy that limits what Mobilicity can do with customer’s Personal Information. Personal
Information includes information about an identifiable individual other than the name, address,
email and Mobilicity phone number, such as credit card information, information collected through
our website or other information we may collect from you from time to time. If you are applying to
come and work with us, your resume and references would also be included as Personal
Information.
USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
Mobilicity may use or collect Personal Information about you to help us provide services to you,
such as to respond to your requests, verify your identity, provide services to you, process
payments, process changes or updates to your account, process warranty or returns, send you
notifications, improve or better our services, customer satisfactory surveys, let you know
information regarding our products or services, develop or enhance our products and services,
manage and develop our business and operations or generally maintain our relationship with you.
We may also use information you provide us, including information about your personal
preferences to provide you with personalized messages and promotions for products and
services. We may select the messages and promotions you receive based on the information you
have provided to us and your previous responses and other communications with us. We may
also use your call usage patterns and the other information you have provided to us to determine
the number and frequency of the messages we send to you.
DISCLOSING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
Mobilicity will never sell your Personal Information to anyone.
Third parties, including parties outside of Canada, may gain access to your Personal Information
or we may disclose your Personal Information to third parties from time to time. For example: we
may disclose your Personal Information to someone who, in our reasonable judgment, we believe
is seeking the information as your agent or your representative; your dealer may have access to
your information while activating, processing, receiving payments or making changes to your
account; another company may be involved in supplying you with some of the services; persons
employed by Mobilicity may gain access to your Personal Information; internet service providers
may gain access to your information; marketing companies may conduct research or other
analysis. In addition, your Personal Information including your location may be disclosed to
public authorities, for example when you make a 911 call. We may also collect, use and disclose
your Personal Information to meet legal and regulatory requirements.
Any disclosure to third parties is made on a confidential basis with the information to be used only
for the purposes for which it was disclosed. Your Personal Information may also be shared if
Proprietary and Confidential                                                                    1

 Privacy Policy
Mobilicity becomes part of a merger, amalgamation, or otherwise sells its business or part of its
business.
PROTECTING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
We use standard industry standards to safeguard the confidentiality of your Personal Information.
We use a variety of physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal
information. We do not warrant that the safeguards we implemented are sufficient to protect
Personal Information you transmit over the internet. Most of your Personal Information are store
within Canada. Some companies providing services to Mobilicity may be located outside of
Canada (including the U.S.A.) and your Personal Information may be stored in those jurisdictions
and as such, your Personal Information may be made available to the government or its agencies
under a lawful order made in that country (including the U.S.A.). For further information, please
contact us at 101 Exchange Avenue, Vaughan, Ontario, Canada L4K 5R6 Attention: Privacy or
emailing us at privacy@mobilicity.ca.
YOUR CONSENT
You are consenting to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information by
providing us, our dealers or such other third parties with your Personal Information. We may
contact you by phone, email or text to provide you notifications, promotions, updates or other
information regarding our services and products.
You may withdraw your consent by mailing to us at 101 Exchange Avenue, Vaughan, Ontario,
Canada L4K 5R6 Attention: Privacy or emailing us at privacy@mobilicity.ca. Please understand
that your withdrawal of consent may affect or limit our ability to provide services or products to
you.
Please contact us by mailing your concerns to us at 101 Exchange Avenue, Vaughan, Ontario,
Canada L4K 5R6 Attention: Privacy or emailing us at privacy@mobilicity.ca if you have any
questions or concerns about handling your Personal Information.
Our privacy policy may change from time to time, so please check with us periodically.
Proprietary and Confidential                                                                  2
